Hooh hoooh
Please don't see
just a boy caught up in dreams and fantasies
Please see me
reaching out for someone I can see
Take my hand
let's see where we wake up tomorrow
Best laid plans
sometimes it's just a one night stand
I'd be damned
Cupid's demanding back his arrow
So let's get drunk on our tears and
God, tell us the reason
youth is wasted on the young
It's hunting season
and the lambs are on the run
Searching for meaning
But are we all lost stars,
trying to light up the dark?
Who are we?
Just a spec of dust within the galaxy
Woe is me
if we're not careful turns into reality
Don't you dare
let all these memories bring you sorrow
Yesterday
I saw a lion kiss a deer
Turn the page
maybe we'll find a brand new ending
Where we're dancing in our tears and
God, tell us the reason
youth is wasted on the young
It's hunting season
and the lambs are on the run
Searching for meaning
But are we all lost stars,
trying to light up the dark?
Hoo hoo hoo
And I thought I saw you out there crying
Hoo hoo
And I thought I heard you call my name
Yeah Yeah
And I thought I heard you out there crying
Oh Just the same
Oh Yeah... yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
God, give us the reason
youth is wasted on the young
It's hunting season
and these lambs are on the run
Searching for meaning
But are we all lost stars,
trying to light, light up the dark?
Hoo hoo
And I thought I saw you out there crying
And I thought I heard you call my name
Hoo hooo
And I thought I heard you out there crying
Oh but are we all lost stars,
trying to light up the dark?
Are we all lost stars,